{
    "Stacks": [
        { "Id": 1, "Name": "French" },
        { "Id": 2, "Name": "Italian" },
        { "Id": 3, "Name": "Norwegian" },
        { "Id": 4, "Name": "German" },
        { "Id": 5, "Name": "Spanish" }
    ],
    "Flashcards": [
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Love",
            "Answer": "Amour"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Happiness",
            "Answer": "Bonheur"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Cat",
            "Answer": "Chat"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Flag",
            "Answer": "Drapeau"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Star",
            "Answer": "\u00c9toile"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Flower",
            "Answer": "Fleur"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Ice",
            "Answer": "Glace"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Winter",
            "Answer": "Hiver"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Island",
            "Answer": "\u00cele"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Garden",
            "Answer": "Jardin"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Koala",
            "Answer": "Koala"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Moon",
            "Answer": "Lune"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Sea",
            "Answer": "Mer"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Snow",
            "Answer": "Neige"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Storm",
            "Answer": "Orage"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Rain",
            "Answer": "Pluie"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Sun",
            "Answer": "Soleil"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Mountain",
            "Answer": "Montagne"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "River",
            "Answer": "Rivi\u00e8re"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Cloud",
            "Answer": "Nuage"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Bird",
            "Answer": "Oiseau"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Fish",
            "Answer": "Poisson"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Tree",
            "Answer": "Arbre"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Book",
            "Answer": "Livre"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Car",
            "Answer": "Voiture"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Maison"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Road",
            "Answer": "Route"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Sky",
            "Answer": "Ciel"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Wind",
            "Answer": "Vent"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Light",
            "Answer": "Lumi\u00e8re"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Darkness",
            "Answer": "Obscurit\u00e9"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Morning",
            "Answer": "Matin"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Evening",
            "Answer": "Soir"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Night",
            "Answer": "Nuit"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Spring",
            "Answer": "Printemps"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Summer",
            "Answer": "\u00c9t\u00e9"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Autumn",
            "Answer": "Automne"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 1,
            "Question": "Day",
            "Answer": "Jour"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Love",
            "Answer": "Amore"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Happiness",
            "Answer": "Felicit\u00e0"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Cat",
            "Answer": "Gatto"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Flag",
            "Answer": "Bandiera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Star",
            "Answer": "Stella"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Flower",
            "Answer": "Fiore"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Ice",
            "Answer": "Ghiaccio"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Winter",
            "Answer": "Inverno"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Island",
            "Answer": "Isola"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Garden",
            "Answer": "Giardino"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Koala",
            "Answer": "Koala"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Moon",
            "Answer": "Luna"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Sea",
            "Answer": "Mare"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Snow",
            "Answer": "Neve"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Storm",
            "Answer": "Tempesta"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Rain",
            "Answer": "Pioggia"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Sun",
            "Answer": "Sole"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Mountain",
            "Answer": "Montagna"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "River",
            "Answer": "Fiume"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Cloud",
            "Answer": "Nuvola"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Bird",
            "Answer": "Uccello"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Fish",
            "Answer": "Pesce"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Tree",
            "Answer": "Albero"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Book",
            "Answer": "Libro"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Car",
            "Answer": "Auto"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Casa"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Road",
            "Answer": "Strada"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Sky",
            "Answer": "Cielo"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Wind",
            "Answer": "Vento"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Light",
            "Answer": "Luce"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Darkness",
            "Answer": "Oscurit\u00e0"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Morning",
            "Answer": "Mattina"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Evening",
            "Answer": "Sera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Night",
            "Answer": "Notte"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Spring",
            "Answer": "Primavera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Summer",
            "Answer": "Estate"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Autumn",
            "Answer": "Autunno"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 2,
            "Question": "Day",
            "Answer": "Giorno"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Love",
            "Answer": "Kj\u00e6rlighet"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Happiness",
            "Answer": "Lykke"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Cat",
            "Answer": "Katt"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Flag",
            "Answer": "Flagg"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Star",
            "Answer": "Stjerne"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Flower",
            "Answer": "Blomst"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Ice",
            "Answer": "Is"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Winter",
            "Answer": "Vinter"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Island",
            "Answer": "\u00d8y"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Garden",
            "Answer": "Hage"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Koala",
            "Answer": "Koala"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Moon",
            "Answer": "M\u00e5ne"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Sea",
            "Answer": "Sj\u00f8"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Snow",
            "Answer": "Sn\u00f8"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Storm",
            "Answer": "Storm"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Rain",
            "Answer": "Regn"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Sun",
            "Answer": "Sol"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Mountain",
            "Answer": "Fjell"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "River",
            "Answer": "Elv"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Cloud",
            "Answer": "Sky"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Bird",
            "Answer": "Fugl"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Fish",
            "Answer": "Fisk"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Tree",
            "Answer": "Tre"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Book",
            "Answer": "Bok"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Car",
            "Answer": "Bil"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Hus"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Road",
            "Answer": "Vei"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Sky",
            "Answer": "Himmel"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Wind",
            "Answer": "Vind"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Light",
            "Answer": "Lys"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Darkness",
            "Answer": "M\u00f8rke"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Morning",
            "Answer": "Morgen"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Evening",
            "Answer": "Kveld"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Night",
            "Answer": "Natt"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Spring",
            "Answer": "V\u00e5r"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Summer",
            "Answer": "Sommer"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Autumn",
            "Answer": "H\u00f8st"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 3,
            "Question": "Day",
            "Answer": "Dag"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Love",
            "Answer": "Liebe"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Happiness",
            "Answer": "Gl\u00fcck"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Cat",
            "Answer": "Katze"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Flag",
            "Answer": "Flagge"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Star",
            "Answer": "Stern"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Flower",
            "Answer": "Blume"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Ice",
            "Answer": "Eis"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Winter",
            "Answer": "Winter"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Island",
            "Answer": "Insel"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Garden",
            "Answer": "Garten"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Koala",
            "Answer": "Koala"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Moon",
            "Answer": "Mond"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Sea",
            "Answer": "Meer"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Snow",
            "Answer": "Schnee"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Storm",
            "Answer": "Sturm"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Rain",
            "Answer": "Regen"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Sun",
            "Answer": "Sonne"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Mountain",
            "Answer": "Berg"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "River",
            "Answer": "Fluss"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Cloud",
            "Answer": "Wolke"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Bird",
            "Answer": "Vogel"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Fish",
            "Answer": "Fisch"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Tree",
            "Answer": "Baum"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Book",
            "Answer": "Buch"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Car",
            "Answer": "Auto"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Haus"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Road",
            "Answer": "Stra\u00dfe"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Sky",
            "Answer": "Himmel"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Wind",
            "Answer": "Wind"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Light",
            "Answer": "Licht"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Darkness",
            "Answer": "Dunkelheit"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Morning",
            "Answer": "Morgen"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Evening",
            "Answer": "Abend"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Night",
            "Answer": "Nacht"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Spring",
            "Answer": "Fr\u00fchling"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Summer",
            "Answer": "Sommer"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Autumn",
            "Answer": "Herbst"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 4,
            "Question": "Day",
            "Answer": "Tag"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Love",
            "Answer": "Amor"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Happiness",
            "Answer": "FelicIdad"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Cat",
            "Answer": "Gato"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Flag",
            "Answer": "Bandera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Star",
            "Answer": "Estrella"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Flower",
            "Answer": "Flor"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Ice",
            "Answer": "Hielo"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Winter",
            "Answer": "Invierno"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Island",
            "Answer": "Isla"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Garden",
            "Answer": "Jard\u00edn"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Koala",
            "Answer": "Koala"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Moon",
            "Answer": "Luna"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Sea",
            "Answer": "Mar"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Snow",
            "Answer": "Nieve"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Storm",
            "Answer": "Tormenta"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Rain",
            "Answer": "Lluvia"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Sun",
            "Answer": "Sol"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Mountain",
            "Answer": "Monta\u00f1a"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "River",
            "Answer": "R\u00edo"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Cloud",
            "Answer": "Nube"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Bird",
            "Answer": "P\u00e1jaro"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Fish",
            "Answer": "Pez"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Tree",
            "Answer": "\u00c1rbol"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Book",
            "Answer": "Libro"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Car",
            "Answer": "Coche"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "House",
            "Answer": "Casa"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Road",
            "Answer": "Carretera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Sky",
            "Answer": "Cielo"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Wind",
            "Answer": "Viento"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Light",
            "Answer": "Luz"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Darkness",
            "Answer": "OscurIdad"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Morning",
            "Answer": "Ma\u00f1ana"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Evening",
            "Answer": "Tarde"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Night",
            "Answer": "Noche"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Spring",
            "Answer": "Primavera"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Summer",
            "Answer": "Verano"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Autumn",
            "Answer": "Oto\u00f1o"
        },
        {
            "StackId": 5,
            "Question": "Day",
            "Answer": "D\u00eda"
        }
    ]
}